

Hang Dong

Country Managing Director - Education

Connect

♠ Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

♠ Message

• • •

Hang Dong · 3rd

Country Managing Director - Education

Vietnam \cdot 500+ connections \cdot Contact info

I Can Read Vietnam

University of Social Science & Humanities

People and pages related to Hang

See all



>





Follow



@TeacherToolkit

Page • Education Management 32,821 followers

Follow



Education Development Trust

Page • Education Management 88,302 followers

Follow

About

With over 19 professional working years in Global & Multi International Organizations that allow me to own the Entrepreneur minds & spirit, which shape my leadership with result oriented and dedicated in both sales leaderships, operation Management & business strategy. I went through 14 years experience in retail sales managemen

... see more

Activity

783 followers



I Can Read is honoured and humbled to have been named a Singapore 50...

Hang shared this

2 Reactions

See all activity

Experience

Country Managing Director

I Can Read Vietnam Aug 2017 - Present · 3 yrs 9 mos Vietnam

Wall Street English

2 yrs 7 mos



Apr 2016 – Jul 2017

· 1 yr 4 mos

Vietnam

Key responsibilities: Responsible to lead & manage the sales force team in all schools of Wall Street English Vietnam in Hochiminh City ,the tasks included key followings:

- 1. Ensure sales information system (BRAIN reporting systems) and sales equipment functions (sales kit, welcome packs, brochures, flyers) are developed and utilised for the development of sales capability in all schools in Ho Chi Minh City
- 2. Implement systems and metrics to measure the success of all sales capability development initiatives in all schools

... see more

Deputy Head of Sales Operation

Jan 2015 – Apr 2016

· 1 yr 4 mos

Ho Chi Minh City

- 1) To manage the sales & operation for 3 English schools in assigned zone.
- 2) To recruit, on-boarding & train Center Directors, Sales Managers to run the schools by managing both sales & operation of center to ensure centers hit the service & sales KPIs monthly
- 3) To develop and implement comprehensive annual sales training plan and performance management system that ensure the development of sales skills, knowledge@mobre

Center Sales Director

WallIstreet English Education Company

Jan 2014 – Dec 2014

· 12 mos

Ho Chi Minh City

- ☐ Managing the Center and ensuring everyday smooth operations and delivery to students
- ☐ Ensure that the Wall Street English methodologies and best practice is followed at all times in or achieve consistency with other Center
- ☐ Working closely with the Service Managers and creating a strong partnership between Service (didactic) team and Sales Team, in order to create good synergies
- ☐ Lead the sales team and assuring they achieve set sales targets ... see more

Head of Direct Sales

Wallstreet English Education Jan 2013 – Dec 2013

· 12 mos

Vietnam

- 1. Oversee and manage departmental operating budgets and costs according to annual allocation to ensure efficient usage of resources
- 2. Assign geographical sales territories and establish budgets for Zone Sales Manager.
- 3. Establish and monitor key performance indicators to manage geographical territories' performance to get leads & achieve 35% contribution of sales to the total country's sales

 ... see more

Senior National Sales Training Manager

Avon cosmetics Vietnam LTD Company Feb 2011 – Jan 2013

· 2 yrs

Hochiminh City - Vietnam

□ Management of sales training program execution that include need of course design and content enhancement, establishment & monitoring training metrics, measurement of sales training execution performance, performance feedbacks & behaviors impacts.

□ Recruit, deploy, motivate, reward, manage & develop Division Sales Trainers, Sales Training Assistant, and Zone Sales Managers to deliver current and future sales , recruitment & leadership's development results. ... see more

Show 2 more experiences 🗸

Education

University of Social Science & Humanities

Bachelor's degree, English Language and Literature/Letters 1999 – 2004

Social Science & Humanities University

Bachelor of English, English

Skills & endorsements

Sales Management $.\,12$



Endorsed by 4 of Hang's colleagues at Wall Street English

Direct Sales . 10



Endorsed by 3 of Hang's colleagues at Wall Street English

Sales Operations . q Endorsed by Quynh Anh Truong (Sophie), who is highly skilled at this Wall Street English Endorsed by 3 of Hang's colleagues at Wall Street English Industry Knowledge **Business Planning** . 6 Sales Presentations . 6 **Recruiting** . 5 **Business Strategy** . 4 Sales . 4 Marketing . 4 Selling Skills . 4 Sales Process . 3 **Business Process Management** . 3 **Business Analysis** . 3 **Business Development** . 3 **Project Management** . 3 **Human Resources** . 3 **Marketing Strategy** . 3 Analytical Skills . 3 **Change Management** . 3

Interpersonal Skills Leadership . 5 **Negotiation** . 5 Coaching . 4 Training . 4 **Problem Solving** . 4 Management . 3 Team Building . 3 Time Management . 3 Other Skills 👩 National Sales Training . 3 Multi level marketing . 3 Planning Budgeting & Forecasting . 3 Show less ^

Recommendations

Received (1) Given (0)



Quynh Anh Truong (Sophie)

Head of Learner Discovery at Manabie

June 8, 2017, Quynh Anh reported directly to Hang

I have ever seen any person like Ms.Hang who can work very hard, so result oriented and very creative even working under high pressure. She achieved target sales of whole country consistently and high adaptable to any changes of working environment, she is also initiative for any launches of new products and ... See more

Accomplishments

Language

English

Interests

L'Oréal

B,439,009 followers

Avon



39,588 followers



VinaHR - Top HR Network in Vietnam



36,060 members

Consumer Goods Manufacturer - Confidential

9,659 followers

Jeff Weiner 🛅

Executive Chairman at LinkedIn / Founding Partner Next Play Ventures 10,765,299 followers



People also viewed



We. Tran Thien Truc Giang •3rd HR Director at Wall Street English

Connect



Phan Ha Van •3rd

Managing Director at I Can Read Hanoi

Connect



Thao Nguyen •3rd Head Of Sales & Operations at ACET

Connect



Tran Thao •3rd

Service Operational Management - Open for new work opportunity

Connect



Duy Pham •3rd

Senior Area Sales Manager at Education Group

Connect

Show more Show more

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

Connect			
→Show more			
Add new skills with these courses International Marketing Foundations 2,431 viewers Sales Management Foundations			
81,994 viewers Skills: Learning Retail Sales 57,880 viewers			
Show more on LinkedIn Learning			
Linked in About Accessibility Talent Solutions Community Guidelines			

Student at Ton Duc Thang University

Careers	
Marketing Solutions	
Privacy & Terms ~	
Ad Choices	
Advertising	
Sales Solutions	
Mobile	
Small Business	
Safety Center	
Questions?	
Visit our Help Center.	
Manage your account and privacy	
Go to your Settings.	
Select Language	
(Arabic) العربية	
LinkedIn Corporation © 2021	
	C

...